Mr	O
Justice	O
Anthony	B-PER
Mann	I-PER
agreed	O
with	O
Apple	B-ORG
Computer	I-ORG
's	O
defence	O
that	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
iTunes	O
Music	O
Store	O
is	O
branded	O
,	O
the	O
music	O
it	O
sells	O
is	O
not	O
-	O
"	O
I	O
conclude	O
that	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
Apple	B-ORG
logo	O
...	O
does	O
not	O
suggest	O
a	O
relevant	O
connection	O
with	O
the	O
creative	O
work	O
.	O
"	O

During	O
the	O
case	O
Apple	O
Corps	O
showed	O
the	O
court	O
just	O
how	O
many	O
times	O
the	O
Apple	O
Computer	O
logo	O
appeared	O
during	O
a	O
typical	O
download	O
.	O

The	O
song	O
purchased	O
during	O
the	O
demonstration	O
was	O
Le	O
Freak	O
by	O
Chic	O
.	O

After	O
the	O
case	O
closed	O
Apple	O
Computer	O
CEO	O
Steve	O
Jobs	O
extended	O
an	O
invitation	O
to	O
the	O
record	O
label	O
,	O
"	O
we	O
have	O
always	O
loved	O
the	O
Beatles	O
,	O
and	O
hopefully	O
we	O
can	O
now	O
work	O
together	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
iTunes	O
Music	O
Store	O
"	O
.	O

Apple	O
Corps	O
have	O
decided	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
case	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Appeal	O
.	O

Speaking	O
for	O
Apple	O
Corps	O
,	O
manager	O
Neil	O
Aspinall	O
said	O
,	O
"	O
with	O
great	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
trial	O
judge	O
,	O
we	O
consider	O
he	O
has	O
reached	O
the	O
wrong	O
conclusion	O
.	O
"	O

