"	O
We	O
love	O
the	B-ORG
Beatles	I-ORG
,	O
and	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
painful	O
being	O
at	O
odds	O
with	O
them	O
over	O
these	O
trademarks	O
,	O
"	O
said	O
Apple	B-ORG
Inc.	I-ORG
CEO	O
Steve	B-PER
Jobs	I-PER
.	O

"	O
It	O
feels	O
great	O
to	O
resolve	O
this	O
in	O
a	O
positive	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
way	O
that	O
should	O
remove	O
the	O
potential	O
of	O
further	O
disagreements	O
in	O
the	O
future	O
.	O
"	O

"	O
The	O
years	O
ahead	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
exciting	O
times	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
"	O
said	O
Neil	O
Aspinall	O
,	O
manager	O
of	O
Apple	O
Corps	O
.	O

"	O
We	O
wish	O
Apple	O
Inc.	O
every	O
success	O
and	O
look	O
forward	O
to	O
many	O
years	O
of	O
peaceful	O
co-operation	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
"	O

It	O
was	O
not	O
disclosed	O
whether	O
the	O
Beatles	O
'	O
music	O
catalog	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
deal	O
.	O

