The	O
G7	O
nations	O
had	O
met	O
in	O
Washington	B-LOC
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
that	O
the	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
Monetary	I-ORG
Fund	I-ORG
and	O
the	B-ORG
World	I-ORG
Bank	I-ORG
held	O
their	O
Autumn	O
meetings	O
.	O

The	O
Dow	O
Jones	O
Industrial	O
Average	O
index	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
indexes	O
that	O
have	O
done	O
particularly	O
well	O
today	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
closed	O
up	O
11.08	O
%	O
,	O
well	O
over	O
9,000	O
points	O
.	O

General	O
Motors	O
was	O
the	O
best	O
performer	O
in	O
this	O
index	O
,	O
with	O
its	O
value	O
rising	O
by	O
31.49	O
%	O
.	O

The	O
Nasdaq	O
rose	O
by	O
11.81	O
%	O
.	O

The	O
FTSE	O
100	O
has	O
today	O
gone	O
up	O
in	O
value	O
by	O
8,26	O
%	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
index	O
back	O
over	O
the	O
four	O
thousand	O
mark	O
.	O

TUI	O
Travel	O
was	O
the	O
best	O
performing	O
company	O
in	O
this	O
index	O
.	O

It	O
went	O
up	O
by	O
41.25	O
points	O
(	O
21.48	O
%	O
)	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
new	O
share	O
price	O
of	O
233.25	O
.	O

Some	O
shares	O
in	O
the	O
FTSE	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
have	O
continued	O
to	O
fall	O
dramatically	O
.	O

HBOS	O
today	O
dropped	O
in	O
value	O
by	O
31.48	O
%	O
.	O

The	O
Brazilian	O
Bovespa	O
index	O
today	O
went	O
up	O
by	O
14,66	O
%	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Hang	O
Seng	O
and	O
Singapore	O
Straits	O
Times	O
went	O
up	O
by	O
10.24	O
%	O
and	O
6.57	O
%	O
respectively	O
.	O

Stocks	O
exchanges	O
in	O
Tokyo	O
,	O
Buenos	O
Aires	O
and	O
Toronto	O
were	O
closed	O
due	O
to	O
national	O
holidays	O
.	O

