The	O
bank	O
's	O
CEO	O
,	O
Ken	B-PER
Lewis	I-PER
,	O
said	O
in	O
a	O
statement	O
that	O
''	O
...	O
]	O
credit	O
costs	O
remain	O
high	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
our	O
major	O
financial	O
challenge	O
going	O
forward	O
.	O

However	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
heartened	O
by	O
early	O
positive	O
signs	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
the	O
leveling	O
of	O
delinquencies	O
among	O
our	O
credit	O
card	O
numbers	O
.	O
''	O

Lewis	O
said	O
that	O
losses	O
from	O
loans	O
would	O
probably	O
continue	O
to	O
increase	O
.	O

In	O
a	O
conference	O
call	O
with	O
analysts	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
``	O
based	O
on	O
the	O
]	O
economic	O
scenario	O
,	O
results	O
in	O
the	O
fourth	O
quarter	O
are	O
expected	O
to	O
continue	O
to	O
be	O
challenging	O
as	O
we	O
close	O
the	O
year	O
.	O
''	O

