Ryanair	B-PER	B-ORG
CEO	I-PER
,	I-PER
Michael	I-PER
O'	I-PER
Leary	I-PER
,	O
justified	O
his	O
choice	O
of	O
Boeing	B-ORG
by	O
saying	O
,	O
``	O
The	O
Boeing	O
737-800	O
has	O
the	O
best	O
technical	O
reliability	O
and	O
ensures	O
that	O
Ryanair	B-ORG
is	O
the	O
number	O
one	O
on-time	O
major	O
airline	O
in	O
Europe	B-LOC
''	O
...	O
``	O
In	O
addition	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
the	O
lowest	O
unit	O
operating	O
cost	O
.	O

The	O
addition	O
of	O
these	O
five	O
aircraft	O
will	O
continue	O
to	O
enable	O
us	O
to	O
develop	O
more	O
new	O
routes	O
across	O
Europe	O
and	O
bring	O
low	O
fares	O
to	O
many	O
more	O
European	O
consumers	O
.	O
''	O

Ryanair	O
is	O
the	O
world	O
's	O
most	O
profitable	O
airline	O
,	O
having	O
reported	O
record	O
profits	O
of	O
$	O
269m	O
earlier	O
this	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
pursuing	O
an	O
aggressive	O
expansion	O
plan	O
which	O
will	O
see	O
it	O
's	O
total	O
number	O
of	O
passengers	O
jump	O
to	O
70m	O
over	O
the	O
next	O
few	O
years	O
.	O

At	O
present	O
Ryanair	O
has	O
91	O
aircraft	O
and	O
230	O
on	O
order	O
.	O

