It	O
is	O
expected	O
that	O
the	O
Airbus	O
380	O
will	O
wear	O
the	O
livery	O
of	O
Singapore	B-ORG
Airlines	I-ORG
when	O
it	O
arrives	O
on	O
November	O
11	O
,	O
three	O
days	O
later	O
than	O
originally	O
planned	O
.	O

The	O
massive	O
airliner	O
will	O
then	O
bypass	O
the	O
planned	O
stop	O
in	O
Malaysia	O
,	O
and	O
fly	O
directly	O
to	O
Sydney	O
,	O
then	O
Melbourne	O
and	O
Brisbane	O
as	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
leadup	O
to	O
Qantas	O
'	O
85th	O
birthday	O
celebrations	O
on	O
November	O
16	O
.	O

Qantas	O
plans	O
to	O
commence	O
A380	O
operations	O
starting	O
in	O
April	O
2007	O
.	O

The	O
Malaysia	O
visit	O
will	O
be	O
rescheduled	O
for	O
November	O
17	O
,	O
occurring	O
during	O
the	O
return	O
flight	O
to	O
France	O
.	O

It	O
is	O
unclear	O
whether	O
the	O
originally	O
planned	O
Australian	O
tour	O
dates	O
can	O
be	O
kept	O
,	O
and	O
sources	O
indicate	O
that	O
the	O
airliner	O
's	O
first	O
stop	O
in	O
Brisbane	O
,	O
on	O
November	O
11	O
,	O
maybe	O
eliminated	O
in	O
favour	O
of	O
a	O
brief	O
appearance	O
on	O
November	O
16	O
.	O

