Airbus	B-PER	B-ORG
chief	I-PER
executive	I-PER
Noel	I-PER
Forgeard	I-PER
stated	O
that	O
he	O
expected	O
sales	O
of	O
the	O
aircraft	O
to	O
exceed	O
the	O
250	O
required	O
for	O
the	O
project	O
to	O
break	O
even	O
.	O

To	O
date	O
,	O
149	O
confirmed	O
orders	O
for	O
the	O
aircraft	O
have	O
been	O
received	O
.	O

Airbus	O
has	O
hopes	O
that	O
sales	O
will	O
exceed	O
700	O
.	O

The	O
company	O
is	O
currently	O
in	O
talks	O
with	O
China	O
regarding	O
possible	O
sales	O
there	O
.	O

The	O
first	O
test	O
flight	O
of	O
the	O
aircraft	O
may	O
take	O
place	O
as	O
early	O
as	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
commercial	O
flight	O
is	O
expected	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
in	O
mid-2006	O
from	O
Singapore	O
's	O
Changi	O
Airport	O
.	O

British	O
and	O
American	O
airline	O
Virgin	O
Atlantic	O
has	O
purchased	O
six	O
of	O
these	O
aeroplanes	O
and	O
intend	O
to	O
fit	O
them	O
with	O
gyms	O
and	O
bars	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
seats	O
.	O

