The	O
first	O
flight	O
will	O
take	O
off	O
for	O
a	O
``	O
special	O
charity-flight	O
''	O
from	O
Singapore	B-LOC
and	O
land	O
in	O
Sydney	B-LOC
on	O
October	O
25	O
.	O

Special	O
services	O
will	O
continue	O
from	O
October	O
28	O
.	O

``	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
major	O
milestone	O
for	O
the	O
A380	O
programme	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
like	O
to	O
express	O
my	O
deepest	O
appreciation	O
to	O
all	O
parties	O
concerned	O
.	O

I	O
want	O
to	O
thank	O
our	O
teams	O
and	O
all	O
those	O
who	O
worked	O
hard	O
,	O
days	O
,	O
nights	O
,	O
and	O
week-ends	O
,	O
for	O
their	O
dedication	O
and	O
commitment	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Airbus	O
President	O
and	O
Chief	O
Executive	O
Officer	O
,	O
Tom	O
Enders	O
.	O

